(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-27T22:36:22.810352",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Ugh, 皆さん…
Ugh, everyone...
I don't feel so good.
I feel like I'm gonna collapse...
Like I just went through a freaking portal or...
something crazy just happened.
At least I can see chat. Howdy!
"Poor dad"? No, I'm okay.
Don't you worry about me, I'm fine.
There's a lot of Dead Beats here today.
Dead Beats, KFP members, Takodachis, Ssaladdas...
people...
Uh, let me catch my breath for a minute here.
Ugh, hold on.
That was some crazy traveling that I just did.
I think I went through like a wormhole or something.
It's not my fault that my eyes are... No, hey wait a minute.
Hey...
If you start saying... if it's like that, I swear to God I'll beat you within an inch of your life.
It's fine.
We're supposed to celebrate my 5th anniversary! I'm five!
Can you guys believe I'm five?
Hold on, I probably should adjust the camera a little bit. You can't...
...see me. Hang on.
Oh, you know what? I think I can take control of it if I click... There we go.
Oh.
Hey there!
What's up?
What do you... what do you think?
Do you like it?
You like this new outfit I found myself in?
Oh, "You look cute." Thank you!
A lot of the girls told me I look like a robber...
...which, now that I've said it, you guys, you know, might be able to see it.
But, you know, there are various things that I can do and change with this...
...so...
And "Beautiful." Oh, thank you! "You look amazing." Thank you very much.
"Nice outfit," they say. I'm glad that you like it.
There's... there's many things that I can do...
...but I feel like I should...
You know, a good magician never shows all of their tricks right away...
...you know? So...
I figure we have lots of time to celebrate...
...what is essentially 5 years of all of us being together, right?
So I feel like I should be a little happier about that, right?
Thankfully, I can do something about that.
Yay!
5 years! 5 years!
But, you know, as you guys know, your Mori has like...
...a little bit of a resting B-word face...
...so I kind of have to force myself to smile a little bit. That's okay, I can do that.
I can totally do that.
Teehee!
Oh, wait. Ah, sorry, I grabbed you.
I didn't mean to grab you. What if I...
Peace!
てろ。
Tero.
てへぺろぺろ！
Tehe pero pero!
Hold on, I can do more than that though. That's not...
...I'm not a one-trick pony or anything.
Graaah!
This is my favorite face!
Ebaaa!
Cuz this is how I look all the time off-stream when you don't see me.
It's like I click stream 終わり, and then my eyes just immediately shrink...
It's like I click "stream ends", and then my eyes just immediately shrink...
...to look like this, just so you know.
This is my usual. This is my normal.
My nature.
"So shocked."
"Shock" is one word for it. Toot-toot and Ghost Cats see this...
...every day. You're right, you're right, Deadbeats.
This is the Mommy that they're used to.
And then this is just my current... my constant state of being.
You guys don't mind, right?
Resting B-word face?
No problem, no problem.
Hi!
No, you guys are... I'm just tired, but I'm happy.
I'm happy, but I'm tired.
This is normal, this is usual.
Nope, it's all good.
But someday, we have plans to get like some really good...
...very decent face tracking, so look forward to that.
Oh, by the way, just really quick before we get too in deep into this...
...I have an announcement. There's a special goodie available to you guys.
You guys like goodies? I like goodies. You guys like goodies?
We have...
...a very special item for those of you that use VRChat.
It is a penlight for this specific event that you'll be able to claim.
There's going to be a link in the description. They're updating it as we speak.
And also, there will be a link on Twitter for you guys to grab it.
It's very special. It's got the logo from this specific event.
And I wanted to put it out there. Thankfully, with the help of AEV...
...and VRChat to do something really special for you guys.
It's a claimable item just to celebrate this big event together with you guys.
I hope you guys will enjoy it and use it in VRChat...
...and have lots of fun with your friends if we ever do something like future concerts in VRChat.
I'm always really open to figuring out new tech and stuff like that...
...together with, you know, the other members and all these really amazing...
...technically powerful folks and figure out what more cool creative stuff we can do...
...together in terms of like lives and whatnot...
...this amazing world that we're gonna go explore.
Oh man, it's nostalgic.
It's nostalgic.
Um, I want to do more fun stuff like this.
Is what I've realized after working so hard on this project for so long.
So, um...
So yeah!
Uh, thanks for for being a part of it though, you guys.
Uh, thanks for being a part of it though, you guys.
I feel like I can get even wackier. Hold on.
Expressions... Face expression. Hold on.
Delay!
Wah!
This isn't a me you get to see very often.
And there's also constant sleepiness...
Is this... This too is Sayon's sky.
My beloved. Now I look like her.
Um, we we should move a... I know that we should move along.
Um, we should move a... I know that we should move along.
First, I want to give a really huge thank you to to folks who made this outfit possible.
First, I want to give a really huge thank you to the folks who made this outfit possible.
Thank you so much to...
The designer of this outfit, Nanoless!
You guys know Nanoless?
Nanoless is so amazing and just has the most beautiful outfit designs ever.
And I had wanted to work with Nano for the longest time.
So I'm so glad that I got this outfit fully designed by Nanoless.
Hopefully, we might get like a reference image at some point.
But thank you so much to Nano for creating this outfit.
I love it so dearly. I want to use it in music videos.
Um, so please look forward to to that in the future.
Um, so please look forward to that in the future.
And I also want to give a big ups to Yulie as well, who designed the model for this outfit,
did all the 3D modeling for it.
So Nanoless did the design, and Yulie did the actual 3D modeling.
And neither of those are easy tasks at all.
Um, so thank you for going out of your way to make time for...
uh, just a a little a little 5-year-old Reaper like me.
uh, just a little 5-year-old Reaper like me.
I say 5, I'm actually no number year old, but you get the point.
It's been 5 years together, right?
Um, but yay!
Yulie's so so goated, Nano's so goated. Thank you so much!
Yulie's so goated, Nano's so goated. Thank you so much!
And, of course, this world.
We're gonna get a little bit more into the creation of this world as well, I think.
But before we do that, I want to kind of explore a little bit, you know?
There's stuff to look at around here, you guys. Hold on.
Did Did you guys see... hang on a second. There are a bunch of signs around here.
Did you guys see... hang on a second. There are a bunch of signs around here.
"My Reaper looking extra cute." Thank you!
Your Your Reaper is trying to figure out where the heck we are,
Your Reaper is trying to figure out where the heck we are,
but there are some clues here and there that we can look at, right?
So let's take a look at this. Uh...
I can read.
"Due to a thanatological..." I know Thanatos.
That's a Persona.
"Due to a thanatological..." I know that means death, it's like Latin.
Or something like that, I don't know.
"Thanatological incident, the elevator is out of service.
Whether you are alive or dead, please seek out your local psychopomp."
I know a couple psychopomps.
None of them are in Holo, but maybe someday we'll get a psychopomp.
I feel like we'd be really good friends and get along.
I don't know, 5 years I've been here, we haven't had a psychopomp, but who knows?
In the next 5, we could maybe welcome one.
That would be cool.
"Ame elevator?" See, that's what I'm thinking, I remember this elevator,
even just from the shape of it, right?
"Do not annoy the elevator attendant Ame."
Yeah, no, this is...
This is definitely Ame's elevator, I think.
What happened to it?
You guys know what the heck happened to this place?
"Maximum capacity 12 people, 50 if smol."
Do you guys remember when we had less than 12 people?
'Cause I do. I remember when we had less than 12.
Look at that.
Not everybody would have been able to fit into the elevator.
You know, what about Advent and Justice, right?
They wouldn't be able to fit.
I mean, they could if they were small.
The elevator would need to be renovated so that we could all fit.
Ame, Ame elevator!
Back then, it's been a long time, yeah.
"Time has flown by so fast," says chat.
Time flies when you're having fun, right, guys?
Let's see. "Do not fall into the time vortex.
We don't know what will happen, but it doesn't look good."
Okay, going to heed those wise words.
"Strong quantum fluctuations, keep yourself observed at all times to avoid disappearing."
Eh?
Huh?
What the heck?
I don't want to disappear, I have stuff to do!
Speaking of stuff to do, maybe we should move right along.
'Cause there's some really cool spots around here, and I think I see...
Don't get too excited. Oh gosh, sorry!
I really shook you around a little bit, let me...
I don't mean to do that.
Do not get too excited, but I think I saw...
Get this, Deadbeats.
A resort.
Will Mori Calliope be going there?
Probably... probably... yes, I will for the sake of...
...for the sake of this journey.
We'll go to the resort.
You guys wanna come with, though? I don't wanna go alone, so my Deadbeats gotta come with me, okay?
You guys gotta come with me, is that all right? You guys cool with that?
I could kind of use a rest. It would be nice.
We got some fun surprises today, so please look forward to them.
But I guess we'll try and make our way out of here then, shall we?
Mm. Let's do it.
"We need to observe you to prevent a disappearance."
You make a good point, Skeletons. You make a good point.
Well, let's go ahead and head on over then.
Shall we? What does this say? Hub...
Oh, I can't... sorry, chat's kind of in my way... that's all right. I want you guys here. I want you... I want you here, so...
It's no problem. "HUB AREA" it says. Okay.
Observing... they're observing right now. Okay.
Manotans, do you hear that? They're observing... also Manotans are here today working as hard as possible...
...with cameras and such. Thank you, Manotans.
All right, well, I guess off we go to the resort!
Oh gosh, I don't like going to resorts because, Deadbeats, I feel like...
...I'm gonna give in to my base human instincts...
...instead of my Reaper side, which says work, work, work. My human side says it's time for vacation.
So let me... let's just go. Let me just go and see what happens, you know?
Making my way downtown.
Whoa!
I really need to fix my posture! Haha!
No, it's fine... haha, don't look!
My posture's not the best.
Also, I can walk on water by the way, in case... in case you didn't know.
You guys like my Naruto run? It's just my current state of being and...
And look at your back! Oh wait, did you guys see the design on my back? The skull?
That's my logo! That's my logo. I really wanna release this jacket someday. Wouldn't that be cool?
It'd be a pretty cool jacket to release as merch. I feel like I release too many clothing items, though!
We really don't need that many.
Well, anyway, I guess we better get out of here. Uh...
What am I looking at? Oh gosh, I don't wanna show you guys what the clothes can do yet.
Uh, we'll get to that later, shall we? Okay.
Let us be on our way up the stairs. I'll try to... my posture's great!
I never would bend my back while I walk! That's not something that Mori Calliope would ever do!
Whoa!
Do you guys see this?
This is a full on... this is a full-blown resort! What's... oh.
Hold on a second.
Hey, what's this little switch here? It's got a camera. Can I activate it, I wonder?
Whoa! Check it!
You guys get a sweeping view!
Nice perspective! Anything wrong with your spine? No, it needs relaxation, which is why we've come here to this resort.
It looks like I could run around it like a Dark Souls map. Not everything is Dark Souls, though, just... you know.
There's a bar!
Wait, hold on, I just barely missed... hang on, I gotta fix my knee.
There's a bar, Deadbeats!
Hold on, we're in trouble now.
Hang on, let's get to the center here. Wow!
I don't look very enthused, but I am excited!
Booze! No, wait a minute, Deadbeats! Wait, it's not time yet. It's not time, we have to...
...Bar Mori! Do you guys remember Bar Mori? 'Cause I remember Bar Mori. Oh, that was so fun!
I loved Bar Mori. We should've had more adventures there, but that's on me.
That's on me, I got too busy with other stuff.
My knee's been feeling tired these days... my knee. There we go.
Anyway...
Fancy, classic.
This is not VR Chat, this is a vlog on Calli's vacation...
Wait, no! You got it all wrong! I'm working hard, I promise!
Look at the way that the water reflects off of me, though. Isn't it pretty neat?
Hold on, can I do peace?
Peace.
I'm doing a pose, I'm doing a... peace.
Hope you guys get lots of screenshots, and remember to use...
...#5YearsOfMori to share your favorite screenshots.
Okay? #5YearsOfMori.
You can also share your favorite memories or, you know, fan art, too, if you want. Like, whatever you wanna use.
#5YearsOfMori to celebrate five years of the Grim Reaper invading your personal space.
And by personal, I mean like your home, you know, 'cause when you watch me...
...I'm there, in your home.
Well, I guess we should look around maybe a little bit more.
...Yes.
I dare not...
I dare not lay down.
We don't have time for that, we don't have time...
Let's get moving around a little bit, cause we got stuff to do.
Hang on a sec. Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Yagoo?
Hey, there's a bar over there, though.
There's a bar. Before we get to Yagoo...
Can we just... can we hit the bar really quick?
Hang on. No, this is... this is big. This is big big news.
All right.
Deadbeats, welcome to Bar Mori!
Welcome to Bar Mori— oh, you guys are back here.
I wonder if I can move... Let me get a martini. Wait!
Hang on, I'm pulling you over here.
I'm pulling my chat in front of my face so that I can see them.
Okay, pop, float, and... okay, there we go.
Now I can see you perfectly!
Now I can take your order! What would you guys like?
Can I get some whiskey?
Yes! I actually saved some just for this special occasion, so...
Let me go grab it. Right here.
Yes! Welcome to Bar Mori.
Here it is. Hold... hold to grab... oh, this one.
Hold to grab... Oh, this. Okay, I got it.
No, I— Ah! Wait, I dropped it!
Okay, hold on, hold on...
I'm not very good at this. I...
Maybe I really do need a vacation. Wait, no, okay. Hang on.
The melon soda, see, that's a good choice.
All right, here's...
Got any glasses here?
We don't... um...
Well, all right, chat. This is for you.
Fetch!
It landed perfectly upright!
It landed perfectly. You know what?
This reminds me, I used to tell you guys about my...
...my old job.
I used to have a tough old job...
...that I did back in the day, and I... I served somebody like a drink that didn't have enough like vodka or tequila in it, and they threw it in my face.
I remember telling you guys about that.
Well, I've been through a lot, and I'm ready to unleash my rage!
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa! Something happened. Okay.
Sorry, I had a blackout right there for a second.
All right, is this Amaretto?
Can I juggle it?
Yeah, I can.
Oh man, she's too good! Oh, she's too skilled!
Oh god, I dropped it!
Okay, it's cause I got cocky. This happens all the time for me.
Uh, hang on, I got it. No problem.
"So talented," they say. Big ups.
What do you mean, no, no EN... There's no EN curse.
Stop! Chigau yo!
Stop! No way!
It's coming out of your paycheck. You know what I think about that?
I may have thrown it too far.
Oh, there it goes!
Hey, this is way... this is better than I thought!
Whoa, this is... this is actually very stress-relieving.
Believe it or not.
Yeah, sometimes you just feel like you gotta...
I was supposed to be serving the Deadbeats. Is this the thanks that they get after 5 years of being loyal supporters of the Grim Reaper?
You know what? Yeah, it is!
It's messed up. I have other goodies. I have other goodies for you guys, I promise.
Yes, yes it is. It's so worth it. You guys are too kind to me.
Deadbeats are the kindest. What the heck?
What... Chigau, chigau, chigau!
What... No, no, no!
There's no... Forget your Street Fighter, this is a Trench War.
Hang on, can I pick up this... Whoa!
Oh my god, I can pick up everything!
They freaking killed it with this. Who is "they"? I will tell you shortly.
But anyway, we could play with... I could throw bottles at you guys all day, but we do have to move right along.
Cause we got schedule to keep! Schedule to keep!
All right, let's go check out what the heck happened over here.
Um... what am I looking at?
That's... that's real special.
Right over there, the Yagoo.
Let me see if I can pull you guys up before me again. Get in front of my face.
But yeah, so you can see...
Hang on. I gotcha.
Now, don't be afraid. Don't be afraid, my small lambs.
This man will not hurt you. He's just...
He just has really expensive shorts.
That's... that's my boss, by the way. Michelangelo's Yagoo.
Golden swim trunks. Actually, 24 karat gold swim trunks on my boss.
Good for him, good for him. Thank you for the resort resources.
Hey, is that Justice?!
Cool! We also have paintings of my cute kouhai as well here.
Cool! We also have paintings of my cute junior as well here.
Very nice. And then the architecture— Whoa! Okay, we're not that ancient.
Yo, who made this?
Who made this...
Well, I don't know. What do you guys think?
Ancient Myth.
Oh man, this is where my membership money goes, that Deadbeats write. It sure is.
Right, right here. It's a grand carving such as this.
Myth.
Yes, the oldest and most decrepit and most ancient.
After that, we moved into the... the Promise Age.
"I Promise." Cute!
I love that this one is different in that it looks like...
...it could be a kindergartener's drawing, but it's clearly not.
Like, they made it with intent.
So, it's not... it's not really what it is, but...
Anyway... Let's go, Promise!
And then we also have... Oh, we can't forget them! Advent right here.
There's Advent. Look at all my cute kouhai.
Solidified in history.
What a place of beautiful art.
There's a lot of artisticness that went into this. A lot of artistry.
Oh man, we gotta... we gotta give thanks though...
...to whoever put all of this together, right? Shall we go take a quick look?
Here we go.
"This map was created by SeafoamBoy. Map design and concept art and modelling." And then Maellon.
"Programming and camera systems."
Wow...
Why... why are we looking at this plaque like they're dead or something? Did they die?
I don't think that they died or anything like that.
They did so well though.
I mean, Seafoam's... Seafoam's vision here is just so amazing.
I can see... there's so much nostalgia and love...
...for the 5 years that HoloEN has been together like this.
I just... I think it's such a cool concept...
...and I'm so excited to share all of this with you guys.
It's so, so cool.
Probably one of the coolest things I've ever done in those 5 years...
...is get a place like this.
Get to visit a place like this, right?
And then, of course, we can't forget Maellon, who has helped so much with the programming...
...and the camera systems.
I mean, the camera systems are my favorite part of this whole thing.
Like, normally you can't do all this crazy stuff with cameras, but...
...I am so, so, so grateful.
Thank you so much to you guys for the help and all the programming too.
Man, I... my brain is...
You guys know how my brain is. It's not capable of handling things that programmer brain can handle.
So, I really... I really appreciate it.
Um, and I'm so excited!
I don't look like I'm excited, but I'm excited to get to the rest of it.
So, yay!
We know... Hey, hold on a second.
Well, it's okay, I invited that conversation, so...
...but there's something I wanna... there's something that's been bugging me,
Deadbeats, while we've been here.
Um... it's that I feel like...
...I did something here already.
I feel like I have a memory of being here...
...at a different time.
And I'm not just talking about the fact that it reminds me of the original Myth lobby in many ways,
...but oh wow, I really did just drop drinks everywhere, huh? Okay.
Um, that's kind of messed up.
I really shouldn't have done that. That was very rude of me.
I feel as though I've... I've sung a song here before...
...with friends.
Um, and I want... I'm thinking...
...I might end up remembering that.
I think I sung a couple of songs here.
And so, I think I want to flashback to those if I can.
I feel like if I channel like my inner... my innermost mind, my inner brain...
...then I can have like a "That's So Raven" moment...
...where like you gaze into the future...
...but instead it's the past.
"And life will be a breeze..."
Sorry, sorry!
Anyway, so let me...
...let's do that, everybody.
Let me... Let's go! Flashback!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, come on! Check, check!
on and on, it goes on and on
you gotta let me go, but i'm already -
You gotta let me go, but I'm already...
on and on, it goes on and on
you gotta let me go
でしょ？
Right?
暗くなる頃 始まるパーティー
As it gets dark, the party begins
集まる人種は様々
All kinds of people gather
明日無き夜にダークな遊び
Dark fun on a night with no tomorrow
that's my design さあ創造
That's my design, now creation
刺激が欲しい
I want excitement
命の限り
For as long as I live
迷えるアタシと夜通しいい？
Are you ready to spend all night with lost me?
あらあら あらあら
Oh my, oh my
ホントはずっともう oh oh
Truth is, all this time, oh oh
楽しいフリして aay aay
Pretending to have fun, ay ay
消えたアタシを oh oh
The lost me, oh oh
キミが見つけてね ほら
Make sure you find me, look
ね？ ほら！
See? Look!
フラフラするでしょう
You must be feeling lightheaded
クラクラ来るでしょう
You must be feeling dizzy
ホロホロとろけそう そうでしょう
Ready to melt away, isn't that right?
flash bang
クラクラ来るでしょう
You must be feeling dizzy, right?
そろそろ壊れそう そうでしょう
About to break down, right?
FLASH BANG
Hey! Hey! Come on!
Break it down! FLASH BANG!
Come on, everybody!
FLASH BANG! Yeah yeah, Verse 2!
まどろむ underground (That's right)
Drowsing underground (That's right)
浮ついた解放感 (uh)
Floating feeling of liberation (uh)
剥がれたペルソナ
The stripped-off persona
放り投げ break it down
Throw it away, break it down
だんだん崩れてく感覚
My senses gradually breaking down
染まるのは息する様にカンタン
Getting stained is as easy as breathing
変わっていくアタシ 時は待ったなし
Changing myself, time waits for no one
涙を散らし あらあら あらあら
Scattering tears, my my, my my
いやぁまぁなんか転生した？ uh
Well, like, was I reincarnated? uh
みたいな異世界感
Like a whole different world vibe
纏って違う人みたいだ
Draped in it, feeling like a different person
そりゃあ今日もお美しい
Well, of course you're beautiful today too
出会ったと思ったんだ You choose me
Thought we met, you choose me
けれどあの頃の君はもう
But the you from back then is already
マボロシの様にフッとなくなりそう
Vanishing like a phantom in a flash
それがフラッシュしてバックするんだ
That comes flashing back
目が回るんだ グルグル グルグル
My head is spinning, round and round
本当はきっともう
Truly, surely by now
戻れないよねえ
There's no going back, right?
ちらつく心
My flickering heart
君が探してよ ほら
Come on, search for me
フラフラするでしょう
You must be wobbling, right?
クラクラ来るでしょう
You must be getting dizzy, right?
ホロホロとろけそう そうでしょう
Melting down completely, right?
FLASH BANG
ギラギラ今宵の show
Tonight's dazzling show
さあさあ踊りましょう
Come on, let's dance
真っ白く眩むほど
So bright it turns pure white
ほら焼き付けてよ
Come on, burn it into your memory
FLASH BANG
Nice job, chatcats!
Budge, budge, budge, budge!
Well done. You guys got some moves.
What's she doing?
What is she doing?
Are you good? I was thinking we could use a little rest.
Hey, hey, it's okay.
IRyS, I think you guys need to go relax.
You guys need to go.
Oh, okay! Sounds great!
Have some fun at the resort. You know, there's a cool bar...
Resort time! Bye! Bye, you two!
Oh god, I have a feeling it's about to get real wild back there.
Maybe we should do another song though in the meantime, huh?
Bye guys! They're gone.
They'll have fun, don't worry about them.
Let's, um...
Let's do another song, shall we?
Let's go!
My camouflage
What'cha gonna do? Shit, take a walk!
"Play the role of bad girl" like I had a choice
I could be your "seiso-should-you-say-so", hush my voice
Double take, go figure! A disappearing act
Secret sinners, so you rang? Can't fool me like tick-tick bang.
カモフラ there you go
Camo, there you go
（秘）な逃避行
Secret getaway
どこまでも匿名希望
Remaining completely anonymous
Excuse to see some proof it's me
Flip all that, don't react, eyes right here
Woah-oh!
So crazy, what'chu on?
Predicting all my flaws
But all you're seeing is my camouflage
Woah-overload!
Hey dead beat, why so shocked?
Your Mona Lisa talks
Still ain't nothing new, shit, can't y'all knock?
My camouflage
What'cha gonna do? Shit, take a walk!
Come alive cuz I shift with the scene and vibe
And I dip, shuffle, lean with the moment
Steal a glance, stop, no chance
"This who you gotta be"
カモフラ where you go
Camo, where you go
壁側の向こう
Beyond the side of the wall
すり抜けるこの包囲網
Slipping through this siege net
Excuse to see some proof it's me
Flip all that, don't react, eyes right here
Woah-oh!
So crazy, what'chu on?
Predicting all my flaws
But all you're seeing is my camouflage
Woah-overload!
Hey dead beat, why so shocked?
Your Mona Lisa talks
Still ain't nothing new, shit, can't y'all knock?
My camouflage
What'cha gonna do? Shit, take a walk!
Hey, why so shocked?
Shit, take a walk!
My camouflage
Still ain't nothing new, shit, can't y'all knock?
Can't fight no more...
(Hide away, hide away)
What is this dark side hiding for?
Whoah-oh!
So crazy, what 'chu on? Predicting all my flaws
But all you're seeing is my camouflage
Whoah-overload!
Hey dead beat, why so shocked?
Your Mona Lisa talks
Still ain't nothing new, shit, can't y'all knock?
Whoah-oh!
So crazy, what 'chu on? Predicting all my flaws
But all you're seeing is my camouflage
Whoah-overload!
Hey dead beat, why so shocked?
Your Mona Lisa talks
Still ain't nothing new, shit, can't y'all knock?
My camouflage
What'cha gonna do? Shit, take a walk!
What'cha gonna do? Shit, can't y'all knock?
Guess I gotta use this camouflage!
Wow!
Wow! Wow! Wow! Wow! Wow!
Hi! Oh, thank you guys for dancing with me today!
Wow, and you guys sound so good, too!
Cute! You're really there! Oh my gosh. Oh!
Aw, I'm being hugged! I'm being hugged! Oh my gosh! Aw!
Wait, go enjoy the resort, you guys.
Have fun!
Bye, get some rest! Bye-bye! There are doggy treats over there...
Maybe.
Go find 'em! Go find 'em! They're gonna go look for the treats.
Phew... Maybe... maybe I should relax here for a little bit...
No! We have more songs to do, Dead Beats!
No rest for the wicked. So while my friends are enjoying the resort,
I'm gonna go do some more work.
Just for a little bit, though. We can come back later, right?
Yeah, that's what I'm gonna do. Let me get out of here.
No, no, we can come back later. We can come back later.
I'm out. I'm outskies. I'm out.
Yeah, don't worry about those guys.
Hey, listen, in fairness, don't worry about the Xbox mic either.
I did that to them on purpose.
It was not them, it was me. I cursed their mics with Xbox mic syndrome...
Choking on my own spit.
Because... because...
Their voices are too cute, and they needed to be nerfed. That's all that it was.
But no, it's not their fault. You sure? It was all me.
How dare you! That's fine.
I will take your insults. I will take all of them.
Also, if my friends ever need me to come in for a song and like tank all the bad words, let me know.
I'll do it.
I went through a period in the past five years where I was like...
We can walk and talk. We can walk and talk.
I went through a period of time within the past five years being like:
"You know what? Maybe I should calm down with the curse words."
But it's just because, you know, I'm getting to be an old woman, right?
As you can see, I'm walking like a decrepit, crotchety old lady,
with my shoulders all the way down.
But honestly, if it's for a song, who cares, right?
It's just... just for F-word.
Yeah, speed walking, good old curse words. We stay family friendly here, but...
To be honest...
To be honest, I've heard children use fouler language than I've ever used in my life.
So you know what? It is what it is. It is what it is.
Looks like I'm rapidly roller skating.
Maybe that's what I'm doing. Maybe there are skates on the bottom of these shoes and you guys don't even know.
Anyway, I look like less of a robber, don't you think? Without the beanie?
I look a little bit less like I'm gonna break into your home.
Which is, I don't know, a plus or minus depending upon how you view it, but...
I can take my headphones off, too. Look, they're gone.
They're gone. I don't really know...
I mean, it kind of covers my jewelry, so it's kind of nice that you can see...
the finer details, right?
So I've got like a little skull lapel...
Jacket.
Is it a lapel? Maybe it's just a pin.
I don't know, but I'm really into chokers these days and spikes.
And stuff like that, so...
Yeah. "Law-abiding Reaper." Oh, but of course! But of course.
Definitely.
"Looking respectful." Oh, of course, yeah.
"Checking respect." Yeah, only with respect. With respect.
What do you guys think?
Do you like the inside of my jacket, too?
It's got kind of like a checker pattern. Anyway, we're supposed to be moving...
right along, but I'm kind of taking my time around here as well.
We do have many more memories to... to refamiliarize ourselves with, so...
Let me... let me grab you.
Oh, don't worry. You won't feel it, and it won't hurt.
Okay. I've grabbed you successfully.
Let me... Hold on, swirl eyes? What do those look like?
Hang on. Oh, I'm still on desktop. Okay.
Swirl eyes.
She is a little quirky and crazy.
But it makes me like her more, I guess. I don't know.
You're still here after 5 years, you've definitely got some taste.
All right, let's go ahead and move.
I love the architecture in this place. Lots of respect to the underworldly culture here.
With our... our underworldly maidens.
I don't know who this lady is. Could this be the real Calliope?
Could it be... the real Muse, Calliope?
It could be.
If it isn't, then that's now my headcanon, but...
But I probably should change my... my eyes to not be so swirly. Sorry about that.
I'm just being extra quirky today.
Lore, whom? I'm telling you, I think that it's the original Calliope.
We're going to move with respect, right behind her.
And I wanted to say I saw this before, but I didn't want to get too ahead of myself.
Check this out, guys. Where are we?
What is this place? You can see the sky in the fragments!
But then beyond, there's like a swirling deserted city.
And then I see that there's like... I'm really interested in the hell temple that's over here.
Do you guys see that hell temple?
I think we should go there next.
It reminds me of something that I've seen before, on multiple levels, right?
I think that you guys might be able to draw the links between the places that we're visiting...
...today and also some VR shenanigans that we've gotten down to in the past, right?
But for now... It looks cool! Yeah!
Design is wild, right? Isn't it awesome?
We're going home! On to the next stage, indeed, Deadbeats, indeed. Like from J-Rap & Jigoku...
J-Rap & Jigoku was... was my concert, right?
But Jigoku6 is my EP. Maybe it's not the best idea to use...
...the same word in my concert/shows, because people might get confused.
Anyway, we're going over the bridge to check out what the heck this place is.
I love lanterns, so the aesthetic is pretty much on point for what I enjoy, but...
Hold on. I'm getting that weird feeling again, like I've been here before.
Hang on a sec. Hey, hey, hey. Hold up.
You see that? It's one of those camera signs.
What if we touch it?
Hold on a sec. Let me see that camera...
Camera right here. This should give a sweeping view.
Okay, check it out. Whoa!
Okay, now I'm feeling ultra nostalgic.
Huh? I feel like this isn't the first time that I entered this place, though.
Like I've... I've seen it before.
I think I feel a memory coming on, you guys.
A memory of singing a song with someone here.
Well, if that's the case, then let's... let's check it out!
Oh, this place is pretty cool, too!
Huh? There's cool stuff everywhere!
Especially... this is awesome! It's got lanterns!
What the heck? Didn't I dance in front of that fire during Jigoku6?
Hey, is that the pirate from the Future Island...
...stage that was in the Jigoku6 concert?
It has to be! This place is awesome! This is so cool! What the heck?
Huh? I wonder, are there any friends around here, too?
What friends are here, I wonder?
Are you okay?
Oh, she's climbing up those stairs. I know there's a lot of stairs.
Chimudan, are... are you okay?
I know it's a lot of s-- She's really wheezing.
Oh god, are... are you okay?
Little one, are... are you--
Mori-senpai!
This place is flames!
Hey there.
I can't see much of this, but I can see a lot of things from down here.
You're so cute.
I know you can. I figured as much.
Whoa, hey, don't look too long, though! Don't look too... Whoa, there! Whoa!
She's a little close.
You've got such a big head here.
I didn't expect to see you like this... Oh my Lord!
What, you don't like me?
No, no, I have no problem with that, it's just...
Really, what is it... the ahoge really sticks... Oh my God! Ouch, ouch!
Really, what is it... the ahoge really sticks out... Oh my God! Ouch, ouch!
Why are you beating on me? Hey! Oi, oi, oi...
Why are you beating on me? Hey! Hey, hey, hey...
Get off my head!
Get over! Quick! Quick!
Stop! Stop it!
Get off!
Why are you so crazy?
That's okay, I know the answer. I know the answer.
What's the answer?
I love you so much though.
I love you more, Calliope. I can't wait to...
Oh God.
...do so many things with you.
I want to do some things with you, too, but one of those things is... sing.
One... one, sing on this stage in front of this fire.
Name two!
Um... dance on this stage in front of this fire.
Okay, what's the third one though?
Um, be beside you.
Does that start with kissing me?
Uh, maybe late... We can... Not in front of the people.
Uh, maybe later... We can... Not in front of the people.
Uh, depends on where, too. You can kiss my hand if you want.
Okay, I'll take that!
Okay, yeah, that's...
Perfect, perfect. All right, that's great. So, so sing a little... a little song...
Oh God, I'm flustered now.
All right, let's... let's sing a dang song together.
How about it?
All right, play music!
Check one, two. Hey!
Yay! Hey! Hey!
Mori Calliope! Jijimurin! Let's go!
Are you listening?
Line up, one by one, to play the toy soldiers of a big corporation
兵隊は One by one　私達の言いなり 兵隊
Soldiers one by one, obeying our every command
さあやってやりましょう
Now, let's show them what we've got
Are you entertained now? Let the karma rain down
I can play the hero if it means I'll be the last clown
Living in the twisted diorama that is Industry Fail
And we're in the streets making sales, どうぞ
And we're in the streets making sales, please
今夜も変身　きみら様々
Transforming again tonight, each and every one of you
一緒にあたしと夢見てよ　リカバリー
Dream together with me, recovery
妄想癖　ワールドプレイ　払う
Delusional tendencies, world play, clearing it out
意味とだからぜ
That's why it's meaningful
Let's dig in!
Mirror, mirror, tell me again
If it was stated that I made it on a stroke of luck
Louder, clearer, just say that I'm enough
You lie so well
一触即発　東京！
Touch-and-go in Tokyo!
Yeah, yeah! Hey, are you ready? Go!
Hate to be the one to break the fairytale apart, put the cash to optimism, is what they label "smart"
Jaded, nobody question, stop now and fall behind, every idle beauty got a beast inside of mind
ハイ、注文？
Yes, your order?
Load up the magazine of things you said but didn't mean, it's real in a light full of stains will never clean or wash away
空気感　これですね　一回戦　そんなもんじゃない人生
Atmospheric feeling, this is it, round one, life isn't just about that
勝者ってゲームオーバー　ここからへのギブ
Winners mean game over, giving up from here
雑音　小さく　知恵の勝負
Turn down the noise, a battle of wits
僕僕ではなくなった空間
A space that's no longer just about "me, me"
虚栄自慢をいつもあんた背負い込むの？
Are you always shouldering vanity and boastfulness?
確定モートー　勝因　誰のせい？
Confirmed intention, cause of victory, whose fault is it?
息切れ
Out of breath
余計な雑音多すぎねえ？
Isn't there way too much unnecessary noise?
神目
Divine eyes
割に合わない家事　分かっちゃう惨事
Unrewarding chores, a disaster we all understand
乗れない誰かの今日　高波
Someone's high wave today that we can't ride
渡せ
Hand it over
S.O.S. あたしは
S.O.S., as for me...
誰一人として助けない
I won't save a single soul
Oh, mirror, mirror
ララバイ
Lullaby
死神だって神様の手
Even a reaper is guided by a god's hand
余計なこと言うな　理想郷
Don't speak unnecessary words, utopia
What about this?
Do you like it?
Oh, mirror, mirror
本当のあたしは...
The real me is...
今日もお疲れ様
Good job again today
お疲れ様
Good job
うちだだだだ　仕事しないで
Lazy lazy, don't work
パーティに乗り込み　我を言いたい
Crashing the party, wanting to express myself
払う
Clearing it away
喜ばせて全島を買っていくわ
Pleasing everyone and buying up the whole island
Yeah, breaking down
何だってあたしがいればあかん
Whatever it is, if I'm there it's no good
Hey, hey, hey!
これで肯定した上等な魂
A high-class soul affirmed by this
捨てかけをクロスな同格
Crossing equal status on what's cast aside
Go, dig it, dig it, good job!
Mic check!
地獄から進行中のアイドル　一投勝負、ドン勝！
An idol advancing straight from hell; one throw showdown, chicken dinner!
Keep it up!
開かれた思考に相当の魅力が思考等！
Substantial charm shining into an open mind!
Excellent!
Cameras to follow the irrelevant, you only gotta celebrate, you only gotta get out of your shell a bit
And if you ever make it better hope that you can take it with yourself, as good as naked, it's a living art, tough to break
I don't care anymore!
It's just business!
Mirror, mirror, tell me again
If it was stated that I made it on a stroke of luck
Louder, clearer, just say that I'm enough
You lie so well
一触即発　東京！
Touch-and-go in Tokyo!
Pair of scythes or hell, am I pretending that I hate it, all the lovin' living life control, let the record spin on like a carousel, oh my God, it's a mad mad world!
いつだってあたしには神様が付いてると問題視される発想
The notion of always having a god on my side being seen as problematic
虚像のまま絶頂の先を鳴らしたいの
I want to ring out beyond the climax while remaining a phantom
Run!
I remember when GG was freaking it! Do you guys?
She was freaking it!
I think it's super cute that...
I get the feeling that only she has chosen to be in that form.
Only GG wanted to be so small and rotund and cute!
Anyway, I guess we should look around a little. She does that all the time.
I see some deadbeats in here who know what's up already.
GG's so special.
Oh, I love... I love her very much.
She's always so nice and fun to hang out with.
I was so glad that I could sing on a stage like this with her.
Speaking of this stage, should we look around a little bit?
Yeah, follow me! What's this?
This seems like a really cool view over here.
I love that the lanterns have like this Myth logo on them. Check it!
Do you guys see? Look! And they glow in like red and yellow...
And you can see so many different areas just from here.
Myth forever, right guys?
You see that place over there? That...
Is that... Is that Atlantis?
I want to go to Atlantis!
Wait, we can't get ahead of ourselves, though. There are a lot of different places to look at, but...
Oh man, I guess we can look at a little bit more of this area.
Let's see...
As I mentioned before in the memory, that pirate...
Is that the pirate from the Future Island performance from Jigoku6?
The concert? I think it is! Look at that big guy!
And it says... I think that's the kanji for "king" on his head.
Oh gosh, there's fire in my eyes!
We don't want to fall down there. But if we did fall down there, something cool might happen.
Maybe there's a secret underneath that fire.
I want to discover the secrets! But there'll be time to look at secrets later, I think.
I'm getting really... getting really hot, deadbeats.
Ugh, I don't feel so good.
But the heat is reminding me of something.
The heat is reminding me that...
I think that...
this wasn't the only performance that I did here.
I think there was another one with two other people.
If I stand here, I might be able to remember.
All right! I think I do!
Okay! Check it out!
Players down in hell all want it the same
Flawless and cautious, oh, what a heckin' shame
清楚なDeathちゃん knows your sick game
Prude Death-chan knows your sick game
Mori
Shake it, I'm a walking disaster
Not half-cocked like the last girl
Ya say stop, I go faster
Talkin' slaughter and laughter, boom boom bang
Act a fool, I'm a misfit
A "too cool" nihilist chick
Think I wanna blow up this niche
Arrogant and loud, I might hit her like a light switch, pow!
I'm such a cosmic pain
魅惑の痛み, shut up, I ain't no hero
Captivating pain, shut up, I ain't no hero
サバイバルできんの？
Can you survive?
Hey, got devils in my brain
Can't make 'em shut up
Next, you'll say you're fed up
Nah, this is what I led ya to
Forget "sport", this is war
What ya waiting for?
Good lord, Mori's bored
Welcome to the killing floor!
Got no will to run
Don't look at me like I'm dumb
Doomers swear "life ain't fair", I don't care!
The end is nigh
End is nigh
Didn't get the memo yet? End is nigh
Boys, line up single file
Wanna end the world in style
Get on some Armageddon stuff like
Gotta kill 'em all から end is nigh
Gotta kill 'em all, and so the end is nigh
Players down in hell all want it the same
Flawless and cautious, oh, what a—
Get a grip, red does not mean "go"
死, not your 虜
Death, not your captive
死 on the new world order's throne
Death on the new world order's throne
Does that make you see the—
Brace for the apocalypse, they hate my guts so read my lips
Don't take the bait, stick to the script
Play 'em like a fool when they numbers dip
Say what now? Make 'em shut down
Yeah, shinigami gang in a rough town
Break new ground, black and blue sound
まだまだぶちかましたい next round!
I still wanna go all out in the next round!
Ah, what's on your mind? Don't want to die?
Price is a little bit of ego
Cynics wanna sit in these robes
Empress got hella new clothes!
Forget "sport", this is war
What ya waiting for?
Good lord, Mori's bored
Welcome to the killing floor!
Life ain't ever fair, but hold up then, what's this?
Naturally that means death is justice!
Lemme liberate you, 世界 hates you
Lemme liberate you, the world hates you
We can make 'em pay too! Ban ba ba ban!
The end is nigh
End is nigh
Didn't get the memo yet? End is nigh
Bring the fire
What if I'm the one this time?
Get on tomorrow, again
Can't stop, I got to kill 'em all
Got to end this night!
Ra-ta-ta-ta-ta!
So go and get on...
...end this night!
Yeah!
Get in, get in, never mind, yeah, end this night!
Cute, something's got to give, gonna burn that wretch in it!
Get on tomorrow, again, can't stop, light, let it all pass like end is night!
Woo!
Yeah, yeah!
Alright!
Big up Raora and IRyS!
Come on!
Ra-ta-ta-ta, end this night!
We Are Currently Experiencing Technical Difficulties. Please Hold!
Whoa! Where am I?
Hang on.
Hang on, guys.
Where... Where are my Deadbeats?
Where... I think I found them.
Hang on.
Ugh... My Deadbeats!
Oh gosh, I feel like I have to go pick up my special camera.
My special camera... I left it...
I left it at the... the other... the other place.
Yeah, that performance was a little too hot, you guys.
Uh, I think it destroyed... destroyed the computer.
It destroyed VRChat. It destroyed everything.
That's how hot of a performance that was.
Hold on. Let's... I bet we can cut through here really quick...
...to get my camera.
Well, you guys know how it's been the past five years.
There's always a little surprise guest...
...some scuff.
I like to believe that EN has moved on from all of that,
but occasionally it will creep back up on me.
That's okay, no problem.
I'm gonna grab the camera.
Okay.
Where'd it go?
Quite the workout, but I got it.
Hello!
As you can see, I'm, um...
What if we just...
I think I got the power to teleport. Oh!
Okay.
Let me get the camera.
What'd you guys think of the Hell Temple?
I figure maybe we can move right along, though.
There are some secrets around the Hell Temple...
that I think we'll leave for a little bit later.
But for now, I wanted to say, do you guys see that hand over here?
What is this?!
This is some end-of-the-world stuff!
Look at that!
Do you see that hand?
It's just, what's the hand doing there?
What if I were to stand on the hand and do some poses?
Maybe we can get some poses of me standing on the hand.
This is like some, some Evangelion stuff.
You know, it's just me and my skeleton at the end of the world, standing on a hand.
What the hand doing? What the hand doing?
Let me pull my Dead Beats closer to me, hang on a sec.
Okay, pull, I'm pulling you closer. I'm reeling you in like you're a fish on a hook.
Giant Skelly!
Yeah, let's grab some screenshots if you want.
This is Mori Calliope posing on a hand.
Wait, I should do something super whimsical.
What if I did a pose with like no eyeballs or something? Hang on.
'Cause that could be fun. No eyes.
What's she doing?
What's she doing on the hand?
What's she doing on... Did you know I could stretch my leg this far?
Oh God, I'm gonna fall!
No, it's no problem. I'm just being super whimsical.
Do a backflip! I can't.
I can't, the tracking is just too, too good over here. It's too good.
It's not possible.
I'm, I'm too busy doing real body tracking.
Uh, anyway, you guys wanna... Let me get my eyes back.
Ugh, it's been a crazy day, huh?
Well, let's... Let's go ahead and check out the city
because there's some stuff here that I wanted to look at, so...
Not just the hand, but...
check this out, what is this little arena over here?
With all this...
debris.
Actually, the word is debris.
Uh, maybe we can get a better look.
Hang on, would you guys like a better look at this place?
'Cause I would like a better look at this place.
What if we... Oh! Hey guys, I found one of those camera thingies.
Uh, if I press this button, we might be able to get...
Ooh!
Check it!
It's a dilap- dilapidated...
dilapidated city.
Is that... Is that big Papa Dead Beat?
Could that be the Papa Reaper up there?
Was Advent held here? You would think, right?
See, that's the kind of vibe that I'm getting from this place, this dilapidated city.
And that's a Dead Beat being chained by his neck.
Maybe we could save him, I feel bad.
"That's actually my house." Oh God, I'm sorry, Dead Beat!
I didn't mean to show your house like that in front of everybody.
I'm sorry. Wait, that was an accident.
Aw, but look, this...
People really could live here.
Would I choose to live... Maybe I should build my house here.
'Cause I'm looking into building a house. Right, Dead Beats? I mentioned that.
Maybe I should build my house here.
Oh! You guys wanna see something cool, actually?
Uh, there's something that I haven't showed you I can do with this outfit.
You're really close. I'm really close to you. Hi.
Um, check this out. Hold on.
I'm changing, don't look.
Okay, here we go!
No jacket!
No jacket Mori Calliope!
Check it out! My hands are doing funny things.
Did you know that I have... I have 50 extra tendons in my hands?
Uh, peace sign. Let me do a peace. Peace!
Handycam! Gasp, shoulders exposed!
No way!
It looks pretty cool, though, perfect for summertime, right?
Although I get the feeling if I put on the beanie, I would definitely look like a robber.
In that case, what can you do?
Nothing much to... Summer just ended, did it really?
I don't feel like it's ended. I feel like we still got a ways to go, but...
get back to the relevant subject here.
Back to the relevant subject, we're in this dilapidated city.
Isn't this cool?
I'd love to just rest my legs, but I feel like...
another memory's coming on, you know?
Another like "I've been here before and sang some songs with some friends."
So, would you guys like to see that?
Maybe we can both have a brain blast together.
Channel your, your third eye. Channel the inner part of your brain
to remember things that you forgot.
do more often.
It'll be very helpful for me.
But anyway,
let's go ahead and run the memory!
Cut your other ties
This ain't the only battlefield I can televise
Ego is an armor, so put the camera down and face it
They went and got complacent
Come in and run with me
You say you stand for nothing, no one else can relate
Just know the company you keep is in the business of hate
Are you afraid?
Run away, I'm close to getting paid
I'll be dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest
Going: "Shoot, shoot, shoot"
Oh, baby, did you miss?
Ricochet, ricochet, you can think about me anytime of any day
Forget your street fights
This a trench war
I'll make you march, march, march 'til you hit the floor
Getting thirsty for collision, let them wonder what they're missing
In the front row
Lock-and-load, now here we go
This ain't a lifeline
It's a call to arms
Become the reason, the unforgiven
Make a decision
If you're looking for permission to riot, you got it wrong
Say goodbye to your identity, click, flash, now you belong
The situation isn't fluid at all
Took out my reddest paints and markers and I ruined the wall
It's not that complicated I could choose to run but I crawl
To slit the ankles of the skeptics who are wishing we fall
I'll be dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest
Going: "Shoot, shoot, shoot"
Oh, baby, did you miss?
Ricochet, ricochet, you can think about me anytime of any day
Forget your street fights
This a trench war
I'll make you march, march, march 'til you hit the floor
Getting thirsty for collision, let them wonder what they're missing
In the front row
Lock-and-load, now here we go
This ain't a lifeline
It's a call to arms
Become the reason, the unforgiven
Make a decision
If you're looking for permission to riot, you got it wrong
Say goodbye to your identity, click, flash, now you belong
I'll be dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest
Make it shoot, shoot, shoot and we'll see who shoots the best
Fighting all our battles never turned out well
They go "ready, set, rage" then they follow us to hell
Finger on the trigger, about to cock it and run
Got a lyric in the chamber but I'm aiming my own gun
Forget your street fights
This a trench war
I'll make you march, march, march 'til you hit the floor
Getting thirsty for collision, let them wonder what they're missing
In the front row
Lock-and-load, now here we go
This ain't a lifeline
It's a call to arms
Become the reason, the unforgiven
Make a decision
If you're looking for permission to riot, you got it wrong
Say goodbye to your identity, click, flash, now you belong
Let them riot onward, lock-and-load
Stand for nothing, play the coward
Stand for someone you'll devour
It's a sick and twisted miscreant's existence
Let them riot onward, lock-and-load
Stand for nothing, play the coward
Stand for someone you'll devour
It's a sick and twisted miscreant's existence
Errors creeping through the core
Protocols failing
System collapse in three, two, one
雑音の Noise のない歪が
Distortion without any noise,
Trust, Faith, そう何一つ Delete
Trust, faith, yeah, delete every single one.
モラルも正義もただの概念
Morals and justice are merely concepts.
Shut it down, I rewrite what is mine
精神を蝕む Paranoia
Paranoia eroding the mind,
Just 1 shot 逃げ場無く貫ける
Just 1 shot, piercing through with nowhere to run.
偽光、絶望、不完全コード
Fake light, despair, incomplete code,
Glitching mind, Rewrite, rewrite, rewrite, rewrite
何度奪われても
No matter how many times it's stolen,
何度壊されても
no matter how many times it's broken,
それでもまだ
even so, still...
届かない
Cannot reach...
抗い
Resist...
進め
Advance...
混沌を宿して
Harboring chaos...
Override, override, ゼロの光を宿す意味を続けよう
Override, override; let's carry on the meaning of harboring zero light.
この壊れた世界で証明を叫ぶ
Screaming our proof in this broken world!
No rewind, no reset, 奇跡の先に咲く花が...
No rewind, no reset; the flower that blooms beyond miracles...
ループじゃない 選んだ道だ
It's not a loop, it's the path I chose.
I fall, I rise, I overwrite
We fall, we rise, we overwrite
Fading exponentially
Can't expect more than a pair
Lost inside nightmare, shed the fear
Strip away glitching emotions, make a stand
In the end, going nowhere, drowning loops
What if the truth lies, gotta break the chain!
だけど描くの Firewall
But I'll draw a firewall
Just 1 or 0, go get クリアを
Just 1 or 0, go get clear
Cry out, break down, 壊す Broken dream
Cry out, break down, destroy the broken dream
Re-wire, re-wire, re-wire, re-wire
選ぶ散らばる
Chosen, scattered...
何度閉ざされても
no matter how many times we are shut out,
この手でまた
with these hands, once again...
描け
draw it,
終焉を飛び越え
jump over the end.
Overwrite, overwrite
愛の中からの光を掴め
Grasp the light from within love.
頼もしき仲間達に
To our reliable companions,
真実を飾らせ
let the truth adorn them.
No rewind, no reset, 選ばれた道に
No rewind, no reset, on the chosen path,
模索はない
there's no searching in the dark.
ループじゃない 選んだ道だ
It's not a loop, it's the path I chose.
I fall, I rise, I overwrite
We fall, we rise, we overwrite
壊した世界で
In the destroyed world,
声だけが響いていた
only voices echoed.
Dead code を焼き尽くせ
Burn the dead code to cinders,
限界を蹴り飛ばせ
kick past your limits,
宿命をねじ伏せろ
overpower destiny,
Throw away all despair, NO!
Overwrite, overwrite
ゼロの声響く
The voice of zero echoes,
声を上げろ
raise your voice,
この痛みを抱いて
Embrace this pain,
最果てへ向かえ
and head for the absolute end.
No rewind, no reset, カオスの先に
No rewind, no reset, beyond the chaos,
咲く花がある
there are flowers blooming.
ループじゃない 選んだ道だ
It's not a loop, it's the path I chose.
I fall, I rise, I overwrite
We fall, we rise, we overwrite
She died!
Do you guys remember when Nerissa Ravencroft died?
Cuz I do!
These have been really fun, these memories.
These memories have been really fun.
I've really enjoyed looking through them with you guys.
I saw somebody in chat said "Help, is she on desktop?"
I saw someone in chat say "Help, is she on desktop?"
No, she's in the world with us!
But you know, a desktop is very helpful for folks
who cannot be present in the exact place
or do not have full body capabilities at the moment.
But you know, I think despite all the technical...
...technical walls that we've had,
bringing this nostalgic trip down memory lane to light,
everything has been so interesting and fun the whole time,
and I'm just so happy to be able to spend that with you guys,
to show you guys this amazing creation.
Look at that Dead Beat! Look at me and the Dead Beat.
Don't be shy, come back.
There's the Dead Beat.
There's the Dead Beat!
That's a Dead Beat.
That's a Dead Beat for ya!
"Mori Calliope peak." I like that.
Can we start using that?
You can if you want. I won't say it, but if you want to.
It makes me happy that you enjoy...
What if I jump? I'm jumping.
Seeing if that makes a difference.
In anything, like if the camera can really handle
the full capacity of my jumps.
Anyway, we don't have all the time in the world,
but you know, if we want to look at...
Secrets...
If we want to look at the secrets, we probably gotta get moving a little bit,
but there's one...
There's one special secret that I want to look at
before we move on to the Fated Atlantis,
that I'm really excited about checking out. Do you guys want to go?
If you don't know where it is, you may have noticed,
if you look yonder, if you look way over there,
you can see that there's a black square in the cliff side.
you can see that there's a black square in the cliffside.
Way over there in the cliff side of the plaza.
Way over there on the cliffside of the plaza.
So I was thinking maybe we could go there.
There's a little secret over here.
Perhaps it leads to another memory?
I don't know, I'm kind of nervous.
I feel like, what if we're not able to get back? I mean...
The ominous square in the wall...
Typically, if you see a hidden wall... visions of hidden walls. Maybe I should roll through,
like Dark Souls.
Walk on water...
Anyway, anyway.
Shall we go inside?
Whoa!
Hey...
I know this place.
Do you guys know this place?
Do you guys remember?
Oh man, it's been a really long time, huh?
I know it. Some of you were around for this, but...
Remember when we had one of our... aww.
And see the banner: "Happy HoloMyth 2 year anniversary!"
Blast from the past, right? For the memories.
Remember when we all sang and danced in an interesting way on this stage?
And I remember we had so many things to announce back then,
and we did it in 360, too!
So like people could use their phone and like sit in the center and like rotate it around,
and they could look at their oshi the whole time!
I wonder how many Dead Beats were lookin' mostly at Mori.
You don't have to, though, because there are so many wonderful people to enjoy and support, but...
but if you did look at me lots, I'd be really happy.
I wanna do something like that again someday, actually.
Kind of walking around this old place and thinking that to myself, you know, like...
It'd be really cool to do something like that again.
And we can't forget the backstage, right? You guys were allowed backstage,
which is very special, don't you think?
Hold on. Whoa!
Remember we had you guys sit... we had you guys sit right there,
on this stool.
In this exact spot.
Back in the day.
It's all kind of dark and dimly lit now.
Since it was so long ago, somehow it still feels like home, you know?
I'd really love... I'd love for you guys to be able to visit this spot, too.
But maybe you'll be able to.
Well, we'll talk about that a little bit later, but...
Ah, guess we better get out of here. We got an Atlantis to look at!
So let's get... let's get moving, I guess.
As much as I would love to sit here and just reminisce about everything that's happened, right?
I think maybe we should go ahead and get moving.
Before I get too sentimental.
All right.
Let's go!
I'm happy you're with us, Calli.
I'm happy I'm here.
Thank you for making it fun to be here.
Well, it's a happy occasion, right?
We should be happy and excited for the future.
So let's go! We're going, we're going.
But a moment of quiet reflection is fun, too, don't you think? I think so.
The way to Atlantis is kind of far, so I hope you guys can keep up with me.
Get running, Dead Beats! We're running, we're running!
All this training I've been doing, and I still feel like I'm not in enough shape to be doing this!
But we're going, we're going. Atlantis time, Atlantis time!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Yagoo!
Oh, here we are.
Tada! Okay.
This is another one of those... ooh.
Check this out. Whoa!
That's Atlantis! Atlantis, finally, at last!
We get to see it! I feel like this is based off of a room of a good friend of mine.
Do you guys remember Gura's Atlantis room?
It was based off of her. Kind of makes me think of that.
Hey, but what the heck is Council... Is that Council Rys?
It might be Council Rys, I'm not totally sure, but...
Before we jump in there,
I'm getting the feeling that I've entered this place before.
Well, shall we go ahead and take a look at another couple of musical memories
before we get too deep into exploring, shall we?
All right, Dead Beats!
Play... run... run the memory... I'm having a brain split! If you could gaze into the past...
Here it goes!
Is this supposed to be Atlantis?
Heh, so many memories.
I remember Atlantis.
I remember all the places that we had...
...in the original VRC Myth map.
This brings back a lot of memories.
There's something kind of different, though.
Right? There's something kind of different about this place.
Who are those people over there?
Oh, I know these people!
Familiar faces all around me.
Familiar faces...
I wanna sing a song with someone here, though.
Who will I sing with here, I wonder?
Mori! Mori-senpai!
Wait a minute, what? Is that... is that Shiori?
Look down here!
Wait, I see a rock! There's a rock way up there!
Yeah! I'm coming down!
I see a rock!
I'm coming down!
Yeah, come on down!
Yeah, no prob- There's a lot of stairs!
Okay, I guess she doesn't care about the stairs.
Oh god!
What the-
Dang, you freaking came in like a wrecking ball there.
Hi, Shiori.
Hello!
You're so small!
Nice, nice outfit!
Thank you! My brand new duds. What do you think?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Whoa there, don't get too close. There's a zipper, hold on.
It's so cozy!
No, no, no. You're not the first person to do this today.
Oh god.
Look at your outfit! Look at you, you look so nice!
Thank you, I appreciate it.
We look like we're in the same band or something.
What the heck? Look at her, she's voguing!
Oh my- I can vogue too!
Aha! Aha! Aha!
No, I'm not as good as she is.
But you know what? I think we should sing together.
Yeah! Let's sing a song together!
We should sing a really intense hard rock song.
Like camping?
Uh, no... no camping, no camping.
You get it? 'Cause in-tents? Like camping?
Oh god... Shiori!
You're reminding me of Ina with the puns. I should smack you.
I'll be serious! Let's sing something...
Yeah, just serious enough, right?
All right!
Let's run it then!
Play music!
Start!
テメェの所為です
It's all your fucking fault!
どの子が好き？
"Which girl do you like?"
この子に決めた
"Well, I've chosen this one."
角度を調節
Adjust the angle
覚悟 微調整
Preparation, the fine-tuning
飽きたらポイから
Since you can just toss her when you're tired of her
place any bets
decide who is special and discard the rest
gambler by nature
chips start to stack
racing lovely animals until they crack
やいの やいの
Aren't you persistent!
貼り付け parasite
You clingy parasite
ヤンデレッテル
Going crazy,
テメェの所為です
and it's your fucking fault
black out , break down
Black out, break down
toss it when you've had enough
やっちゃえ いっちゃえ
Go, go, go on now!
i can tell you 're not impressed
I can tell you're not impressed
右向け右
Face to the right now
左向け左
Now to the left, left
leave the defective , unworthy of investment
Leave the defective, unworthy of investment
飽きたらポイから
Since you can throw me away when you're tired, I'm a-
hot mess , worthless doll
Hot mess, worthless doll
よってたかって いらっしゃい
- Blindly following the others
gambler by nature
chips start to stack
racing lovely animals until they crack
beautiful dreams await modest hearts
close your eyes and all you'll see is black
才能
Talent -
サイコパスと紙一重
There's a fine line between "talented" and "psychopath"!
やってちまったの後悔で fever
A fever that comes with regretting your actions
もういい！ starving!
"I've had enough!" "I'm starving!"
時間のムダ 無駄
What a waste of time!
やっちゃえ いっちゃえ
Go, go, go on now!
i can tell you 're not impressed
I can tell you're not impressed
ウゼェ バカ アホ カス
Disgusting, stupid, idiot, trash
こちら最下層
We are the lowest of the low
どうにか成りそう
I think I can manage
どうにでも成りそう
But it could go either way
ぶっとい絆
Strong ties, yet -
lonely lonely
trouble in paradise
oh, if only
愛を唱えて
Sing of love
「あいうえお」から「ん」まで昇って
"Aiueo" up to "n"
見下してやるわ
From there, I'll look down at you
やいの やいの
Aren't you persistent!
貼り付け parasite
You clingy parasite
ヤンデレッテル
Going crazy,
テメェの所為です
and it's your fucking fault
black out , break down
Black out, break down
toss it when you 're out of love
Toss it when you're out of love
やっちゃえ いっちゃえ
Go, go, go on now!
i 'm the one that 's not impressed
I'm the one that's not impressed
ひでぇ... 咲き誇り
Cruel... blooming in full,
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah...
灰色の世界で花開くは
What blossoms in a gray world is...
Ah...
Woah...
Yeah!
Guess I took a leap, no turning back point to go
Looking deep inside for the cheat to exploit, you know
あいつ も こいつ も そいつ も どいつ も driving me crazy
Every single one of them is driving me crazy
Wanted, wasted, sorry-lookin' faced kid, can't stop falling down
Wanted, wasted, sorry-looking-faced kid, can't stop falling down
Tell me how I'm worthless, show ya where the dirt is
One man's trash is another man's purpose
Day one, flying high, come tomorrow, let me die
Talk trash, choke on wine, nothing I own is truly mine
ごっくん
Gulp
愛されたいのに
I want to be loved, yet
会えない夢を見てるのはなんで？
why am I dreaming of dreams where I can't meet you?
Woah...
変えたい現実
Reality I want to change
胸糞悪くて high になる
feels sickeningly awful, getting high
やっちゃって やっちゃって やっちゃって そのまま傷つけちゃって
Just doing it, just doing it, just doing it, hurting people just like that
期待裏切る bad ending
A bad ending betraying expectations
円から抜け出せない
Can't escape from the circle
エンドロール
End roll
演者は揃いも揃って
All the performers gathered together
クズに仕上げて頂戴
Make me into scum, please
整合性
Consistency
正当性
Legitimacy
正義の名の下
In the name of justice
下してやるわ
I'll bring it down upon you
Game maker
Undertaker
脳天直下
Straight down to the crown of your head
くらえー
Eat this!
アンアン アンアン
An-an, an-an
響け
Resound
Mayday, Mayday
タンタン タンタン
Tan-tan, tan-tan
鳴らす
Ringing out
聞こえないふりして
Pretending not to hear
逃げられると思ってんの？
Do you think you can run away?
くそっ
Damn it
愛されたいのに
I want to be loved, yet
会えない夢を見てるのはなんで？
why am I dreaming of dreams where I can't meet you?
Woah...
変えたい現実
Reality I want to change
胸糞悪くて high になる
feels sickeningly awful, getting high
淫らな声で
With a lewd voice
喘ぐ声は
the panting voice
天国に近そうな気がしてた
felt like it was close to heaven
Alright
All night
Anger
狂おしく
Madly
舞い上がっちゃえ
soar up into the sky
OMG! OMG! お前が お前が
OMG! OMG! You, you
OMG! OMG! お前が
OMG! OMG! You
OMG! OMG! お前が お前が
OMG! OMG! You, you
OMG! OMG! 傷つけちゃって
OMG! OMG! Hurting people
足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough
カルマ
Karma
あーもう絶対
Ah, seriously
とにかくいじっておく生身
Just mess with my raw body anyway
愛されたいのに
I want to be loved, yet
会えない夢を見てるのはなんで？
why am I dreaming of dreams where I can't meet you?
Woah...
変えたい現実
Reality I want to change
胸糞悪くて high になる
feels sickeningly awful, getting high
淫らな声で
With a lewd voice
喘ぐ声は
the panting voice
天国に近そうな気がしてた
felt like it was close to heaven
Alright
All night
Anger
狂おしく
Madly
舞い上がっちゃえ
soar up into the sky
Woah...
足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough
Woah...
足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough
Woah...
足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough
Woah...
足りない 足りない 足りない
Not enough, not enough, not enough
Yeah, yeah, Dead Beats, I know you saw that.
You saw staff's hands flying around with the mute button.
Can you guess which memory song we... we sung first?
But in all seriousness... In all seriousness,
I want to give a huge shout-out to all the staff that worked really, really hard
on all of this, because, honestly,
this... this entire production...
Hold on, I'm... I'm working... I got this, okay.
Honestly, this entire production,
the whole team, like, in-studio has been like five people.
And then everybody working on it behind the scenes is like three or so.
Compare that to like...
the 30-plus people that work on the really high-quality productions that
they do for birthdays and stuff like that.
You know, you get one... You get one...
I was gonna say one free one, but you really only get to do one, right?
Which is why I'm so glad that we did this
together, and I'm so grateful that it turned out the way that it did.
But hold on a sec, look!
I want you to look... Oh god, my jacket! Oh, jacket!
Look at everyone! It's CouncilRyS!
This is a bit of a smaller performance area
compared to the others, but look at that Gura trident!
Although I will say...
lady in the back,
is that supposed to be Gura? 'Cause...
there's some differences.
I'm sure that you all can...
Not now. Not now.
Not now. But you never know.
I don't really know if that's something that she cared very much about, but...
Catching strays, catching strays.
Nah, but I look really angry. Hold on, why do I... Dude, there we go.
Oh man.
I hope that my friends who are no longer active with us anymore
are living their best lives out there and doing amazing cool stuff wherever they are,
you know?
That's what I want more than anything.
That would make me happy.
A lot of those faces around us here, too, I really appreciate them. I'm glad I got to get to know them.
And I'll keep watching them in my own way, in my heart.
Stop getting sentimental! It's getting later into the stream, so it's happening. We gotta move along though, we gotta move along,
'cause there's something that I really... I really think I need to show you. There's something really cool.
Follow... follow me.
Off we go. We're moving. We're... We're moving on up.
We're going, we're going out of here.
There's... Oh, but real quick, I wanted to mention something. And I think that this might be a good place for me to announce this.
There's... something... there's a little secret something something below this area. It's related to Mori.
It's related to Mori, but there's a little... a little secret for Dead Beats to check out
underneath this stage.
How would you be able to check it out though if we didn't see it today? Well,
that's because the plan is to release this world in the next few days
to you guys! So that you can hang out here with your friends and explore around and just chill together.
And it'll be so fun! I hope that you guys will have a good time with it and explore and find little secrets,
like what we found, or what we're finding today, so...
Make sure that you get a chance to, and we'll make sure that you guys know where to access it and find it.
So that'll be really fun!
Let's go, let's go. Still things I want to show you.
Oh man, how far...
Oh! You know what? This is the place over here that I was most interested in running towards.
Come on, come on, come on, let's go, let's go!
We're moving, we're schmoving!
Here we go! Guys, did any of you guys see this in the distance?
The... the desert!
The desert!
"The nerd run." Hey, don't say... That's not true! It's a very cool run.
It's a very cool run I'm doing right now. Jeez.
No no no, my walking on the water, no that's totally...
No, chat, don't worry. It's just... Jeez.
No, I'm not... I'm not Jay, man. No, chat, wrong wrong wrong!
You all... "Ame desert???" Yes!
Yeah. It looks kind of gray right now.
But here, let's take a look.
That's an Ame desert.
That's THE Ame desert over there. And that big clock!
Do you guys think... You think there may be something behind the clock?
'Cause I want to go find out. I want to see how far I can... I can dive into this place, but I get the feeling we might find something nice.
Really quick. Hold on a sec.
Oh, I'm excited! I'm excited! What are we gonna find?
"A bus stop?" There IS a bus stop in the middle of the desert! We built one together in Minecraft... I knew it!
It's a dimensional door!
Guys, look!
I found a dimensional door.
Although I kind of had a feeling it would be here, and I may have gotten told by the powers that be that there was something back here.
But shall we go take a look together?
Let me take off this beanie. I'm sick of looking like a rock... It's very cute though.
I mean, the idea was mine to have the beanie on.
Let's go into space together.
More darkness? No no no no.
Whoa, we're in space!
Is it okay for me to be walking on this floor?
I'm not gonna die, right? Hey!
Is this the original bus stop?
This is the original desert bus stop, it feels like. And everything is in the same... the same kind of lower poly style.
Another bus stop? Bus stop.
And then in here, something familiar?
Whoa!
HoloMyth 1 Year.
...Ina timeline.
This I didn't...
This is the original place!
We've got the Ina room.
I feel like I shouldn't be allowed to be here, but...
I want to sit down for like a cup of tea.
The original!
Look at that little Takodachi being so good.
And all Ina's paintings for all of us.
Memories.
Crying YAGOO statue, look at him cry!
We'll go in there in a second.
And then there's my old room! You guys remember my old room?
Huh?
And the moon stage! Wow, from the Hell Temple, it's like the same...
the same style and everything! Remember when I did a Smol concert here?
It's the Mori cave!
It was so fun chilling out here with you guys. I know it's kind of older now and...
a little worn down, but...
I miss this old chill spot.
I wonder if we got all of them here, oh my goodness!
We have time to check out all of them?
What's the time looking like? We're going to have to move on pretty soon, but...
I don't want to, I want to keep looking!
Look! KFP Square!
Oh man, do you guys remember all the fun like Easter-themed stuff or like spring-themed stuff that used to happen? Was there an egg hunt?
I'm pretty sure there was a VRChat egg hunt once...
that we did in this kind of place, and all the little games that we did as well!
Kiara did so much fun VRChat stuff too!
If I remember correctly, memory serves, and I think it does.
Memory serves correctly.
I feel kind of out of place here being in full color, but...
I feel old, dad says.
Aw, it's not that long ago, it's only half a decade.
Let's go to...
What have we got here?
Oh!
I guess that yeah, there was the Ame desert, and then Gumba's room,
which we already checked out Atlantis, but look, you can kind of see...
everything's kind of older and worn out here, and the pillars too are kind of broken, but...
but I remember it!
I remember what this place used to look like.
And it was so fun getting to explore all the different rooms, too.
Aww, I can hear right on time right now.
It's really nostalgic.
Well, I hope that you guys get a chance to enjoy...
this world, cause there was so much love...
put into it...
by Seafoam, thank you so much,
and thank you so much to Maylen as well for working so hard on this, I love it!
I want to do my own exploring later!
And then we can't forget...
You guys, here we are! The original open bar!
It's the bar!
Our old bar where we hung out and...
just chatted the days away!
All the silly, stupid jokes...
in our Smol forms.
Everything's kind of decrepit now, but...
the beginning, right? All the memories.
Movie nights!
We had a lot of fun watch-alongs, didn't we?
Elevator, auditorium...
Remember... oh my gosh, wait! Hold on!
Happy HoloMyth 1st Anniversary?
Four years ago!
Hi Mom!
Hey Deadbeats!
Look at how much I've grown!
We've all grown, haven't we?
Everybody was crying cause we couldn't meet each other.
And then we did!
Man, half a decade, huh?
We should get out of here before I get too emo.
Funny walk, funny run, ah, so silly!
We got barely any time left, but...
I'm sure it'll be okay.
One last thing I wanted to show you is this place.
It's the ship!
Sunfish ship!
You guys remember this place, too? Remember our Smol adventures together?
Oh man, and we looked out here and we saw Sana was so big!
Yeah.
And then of course our captain was driving here.
...old adventures!
The sunfish!
We should take this baby on a joyride. I'm sure Ame wouldn't mind.
I'm thinking about it though.
Especially after coming back here.
Well... I think we should quick transport back to the desert, guys, since we don't have much time left.
I have teleport abilities though. All I have to do is summon my... Persona. Okay, here we go.
Um, but I hope you guys get a chance to check this place out in more detail, you know?
That would make me really happy.
Ah, we're back!
Because... I feel like after all that we've...
...looked at so far and all the memories that we've experienced...
...there's a special song that I want to sing here.
But I have the feeling I already sang it.
Well then, shall we remember?
Let's go.
Last Days
[Title: Last Days]
Castle made of thorns
Moon that rose in crimson
Grab for something more
All I get is distance
Driving roadless
Feels like the end of a life
Running through those nights
All I saw were curses, stuck here unalive
Floating on the surface, still and shallow
Probably left to rot, I'm sinking
So close to giving up, giving out, giving in
Could I still live again, live again, live again?
But what's the point in fighting when nothing lasts at all?
On your last day
Standing here alone with you, I found my vision was
Way off, way off
Now I can't wake up, wake up
Don't tell me it's over, it must be
Is it gonna be just me left behind?
Me and my mind, forever wasting time
Back then there was nothing left to lose
Back then every night was wine and blues
That's when every pen I tried to use
Ended up leaking my weakness and bled through
All in, but still a little mistaken
Faking like I knew the risk taken
Wakin' up every night pacing
Was it all a waste, then? Am I worth replacing?
Locked down deep in my soul is what I really
Want to shout now, out of control
But I still hold it inside
And now there's nowhere to hide
You wanna know if I'm fine, well
At least nobody's died
So close to giving up, giving out, giving in
Could I still live again, live again, live again?
But what's the point in fighting when nothing lasts at all?
On your last day
Standing here alone with you, I found my vision was
Way off, way off
Now I can't wake up, wake up
Don't tell me it's over, it must be
Is it gonna be just me left behind?
Me and my mind, forever wasting time
Every now and then
Reality creeps in
I glance over the deep end
You'll live on, still
So when I'm not around
Remember me
Remember what we found
On our last day
Standing here alone with you, cuz nothing lasts forever
Wake up, wake up
No, I can't wake up, wake up
It's not over, it can't be
Is it gonna be just me left behind?
Is this goodbye?
On my last day
Doesn't matter where or when, I swear I'll find us
A way out, way out
So let things play out, play out
Cuz I know
Some dreams just can't come true
But I wanna see you again sometime
That song in my heart, it kept me alive
Hey there, Dead Beats.
Hey there. It's me.
It's okay to be sad.
It's okay to miss the people who changed our lives if they aren't here anymore.
I think... it's okay.
But as long as we have memories, right?
Then I think... maybe...
just maybe it'll be okay even if we never truly move on.
I'm happy that we have memories, right?
And to never, never forget all the stuff that we did together,
'cause we did some really amazing stuff, don't you guys think?
I think we did.
And I don't want to forget any of that,
'cause like I said, I don't really have any plans to get going anytime soon.
But I guess the way that I feel about it is...
I'd like to keep remembering all those people and things that we did fondly,
regardless of anything.
Even through the years, and though they may pass by,
and even when the wounds aren't fresh anymore,
I still... I still want to remember.
I know it's hard to move forward sometimes
when the things that we love and care about are still behind us, right?
Stuck in the past, but...
I'm going to be here to make you smile no matter what.
Right now, there's still stuff I want to do, you know?
And yeah, that's a good point.
Good memories, they should make you sad,
because that means they were truly good.
We did a lot of really good stuff, don't you think?
Well... I'm glad that I sang that here with Ina. I'm really glad.
But there's still some people that I haven't sung with,
so let's head to the final area, shall we?
What if I just... bam! Teleported myself there?
And use my crazy powers of...
Oh, my waist is broken.
That's okay. No, it's fine. All good, all good.
I probably just need to T-pose real quick. Hang on, watch this.
Watch my sick T-pose.
Hang on. I'm already good at this.
I've become a pro at VR Chat in just this short time.
There we go. Fixed!
All right. Time to summon my persona
and head to the final area!
Oh! We're here! We're here!
Oh, where'd my camera go? I lost it.
Is it hiding... Is it behind me?
Oh, I found it! There you are! I found you!
Um, this is one of my favorite areas, I think.
You guys... You guys, look!
What is this? Green fields?
Oh, there's one of those camera thingies. Hang on, okay.
Check this out.
Whoa! It's too beautiful!
Can you guys imagine hanging out with your friends here?
Wouldn't that be so awesome?
I'm running up that hill. I'm running up the hill. Oh, my gosh!
Wait a minute. What's this?
Was Ina painting something here?
I didn't know about that. Heh.
I mean, it is a really nice scenery to paint, I suppose.
Yeah, I guess it makes sense. I'd want to paint here.
So expansive. Oh, sorry, from the sun. Oh, that's okay. It doesn't matter. Um...
So surreal and tranquil.
I guess this is a good place to tell you guys the news about...
a special thing that gets released for anniversary especially.
Do you guys know what it is?
Are we going to run the clip? I think we're going to run the clip.
All right, guys. We have merchandise!
So I created a little commercial before we get to singing here.
Run it, staff-san!
皆ーさん! It's been 5 long years together, but we've done it!
Everyone! It's been 5 long years together, but we've done it!
We made it to Year 5 together,
and while the future's looking pretty crazy and eventful,
let's take a little time to celebrate the story thus far, shall we?
And what better way to do that than with every Holo's bread and butter,
the bane of every Dead Beat's wallet's existence?
That's right, everybody! It's time for premium goods!
Goods, goods, goods! Yeah, premium goods time.
You guys know what time it is. You get ready for it every year, right?
You guys know how I like to release merch that's more on the fashionable side, the practical,
but I think there are a few things that you guys are going to love here.
And remember, if you grab it quick and manage to cop the premium limited set,
you'll get a hand-signed postcard from me!
Mori Calliope! But like always, supplies are extreme...
are limited, so don't miss out, okay?
Okay! Okay! Okay!
First, we got a poster!
I mean, you guys expect posters by now, I think.
You guys are used to posters from me, as every good Dead Beat knows
Mori Calliope is a poster fan and Mori Calliope fans are fans of posters!
I see your rooms. I know.
Not like in a creepy way or anything,
but this one's a bit smaller than the usual huge posters that I always do for these merch drops,
but it's to help with the shipping cost this year.
I don't know, we'll see. Crossing my fingers, but no guarantees.
Throw it into your cart, see what happens, I guess.
I went for an Underworld live show concert poster as a concept here,
and my very own Yukisame-mama created something fun and energetic for the occasion.
So let's reminisce on the amazing shows that we've gotten to experience together
with this big-sized poster!
Yeah, yeah!
Next up, oh man, this one is big!
One of my favorite apparel artists, Crisalys, has graced this humble black T-shirt
with a high quality and subtle design of your Mori,
dressed in grimoire attire, playing her bass, probably a little badly, in an antique shop!
It's the type of shirt where you'll probably get, you know, compliments from fellow quirky folks,
but the average bystander like wouldn't look twice at you kind of deal.
I don't know, again, I can't guarantee exactly what's going to happen.
Anyway, you might find Dead Beats out in the wild, too, so that's fun!
It's just the kind of shirt that subtly expresses your love for Mori Calliope
without being too, you know, in your face, right?
And the design is so so so good!
I owned like five shirts by Crisalys, now I'm about to own six!
Anyway, don't miss out!
Next up, it's a Grimoire Plushie!
Take her everywhere with you! That's what seems to be all the rage these days, right?
And if you give her a squeeze, she says something!
I don't know what yet, but maybe we'll all be a little surprised!
She's got such a cute and huggable design. I'm sure she'll make fast friends with your other plushies,
especially that weird cat, you know?
Maybe you can dress her up and put her in a plastic purse for a day out,
just have fun! I don't know, be whimsical, whatever you want to do!
Finally, it's a concert and live show staple, a casual wristband!
Show your support for your Mori in your everyday life or at a local show,
even if I'm not the one playing!
Something easy to slip on and fun to rock out with!
I want to see all of you guys wearing them at my future shows, okay?
And there's a voice pack, too!
"Mori Takes a Break"? What kind of title is that?
Sounds like some fan fiction to me, but give it a listen, I guess.
Japanese and English voice available.
日本語もあります！
Japanese is also available!
Grab the full set and you will get a foil duplicated stamp on a special postcard!
Be really fast and get your hands on the limited edition set,
and you might just get your hands on a handwritten autograph from Mori Calliope!
Actually, it's not that you might, you will get a handwritten autograph from Mori Calliope if you're fast enough!
We always do gold, though, so how about I sign it with an extra special pink pen?
I don't know, we'll have to see if they let me. Look forward to it!
And again, these are limited to a certain amount.
So if you want to grab a real autograph from your Mori, do not miss out on this chance!
The sales period will run for about a month, so get your premium goods ASAP, okay?
It's like a full-on concert hall over here between poster, T-shirt, squeezable mini Mori, and wristband!
Get ready for lots more shows together, Dead Beats, and thanks for the unforgettable five years!
Yay! Clap clap clap clap clap!
I wonder, how much further can we go together?
I want to see!
Hello!
Thank you so much, everybody! I hope that you guys enjoy the goods. Please look forward to receiving them.
They're very cool! I'm super excited with how they turned out. So make sure that you don't miss it.
I think the shop will open in about six minutes. You'll be able to pre-order your merch and get the limited if you're quick, you gotta be quick,
because they do have a limited number. But yeah, please enjoy!
And thank you always for supporting me so much. There will be a members-only encore after this,
featuring a few more songs and just getting to chat with my members, which I'm excited about. So please look forward to that.
And there's a new song! I should look a little happier about that! There's a new song coming out!
And I haven't really given any hints about what kind of song it is. People are like, "Oh, it's gonna be so emotional, this looks like an emotional song",
but knowing what the song is makes me laugh really hard because it's actually a lot simpler than you think!
But something about my early music is that, man, I was so honest, you know?
And so I wanted to write a song that not just me myself, I as a person could relate to, but anyone,
anyone who has an oshi could relate to.
And so, I hope that you will enjoy it, because it feels like an older Mori song,
while also being a newer Mori song. It's hard to explain,
but I guess you'll just have to watch it and see. MV's really cute, so we'll watch that.
Premiere together, too, so don't go anywhere after the credits!
Please look forward to it! New song, new song! Stream it a lot!
Watch it lots,
and, um, share it around. I don't know, if you want, if you like it.
Um, but I still have one last song memory to replay
in my mind here in this beautiful area.
So shall we run it? The last song of today.
Thank you so much, Deadbeats.
Catch you on the flip side. There might be an after-credits scene...
Let's go!
Lost in thoughts of a frosted frame of mind
Honest to God, it's just not our time
Promises flawed by cosmic design
これくらいどうってことない
It's really no big deal at all,
でも涙の跡は消せない
but the traces of tears cannot be erased.
Coming of age, the stage doesn't light up
Just right away, they told us it might've
夢はもう諦めます
I'll give up on my dream already.
This cynical mind says "Why'd you try?"
"Why not give up and play the bad guy?"
分かってるさ
I know that.
運命が波立てながら 貴方飲もうとするのなら
Even if fate stirs up the waves and tries to swallow you whole,
崩れ落ちそうな身体 抱きしめるから
I'll hold your crumbling body tight.
We choose to know
The struggles of this scuffed up page we're living in
The struggles of this scuffed-up page we're living in
腐ったクズの日々だけど
Even though these rotten days are like scum,
この夜明け could seem a lot like "not your day"
this dawn could seem a lot like "not your day."
それでも貴方を捨ててしまわないで
Even so, don't throw away who you are.
Can't find a reason to stay
Some busted world led astray
Once trusted, left to decay
We choose to go on anyway
Lost in thoughts of always changing pace
Allies and friends hiding more than one face
Not really surprising, why are you compromising?
The sun is rising, a new horizon
With friendships lacking lies and
The knives in your back, so what are you prioritizing?
You aren't sick of crying? See, I don't buy it
But here we are, hanging on, fighting strong despite it
「儚い」じゃ表し切れない
It can't be expressed as just "fleeting"
もう目を閉じてしまいたいくらいの暗い
in a world so dark that I just want to close my eyes.
This cynical mind says "Why'd you try?"
"Why not give up and play the bad guy?"
分からないんだ
I don't understand.
埃まみれの街で 貴方のため息の影
In this dust-covered town, the shadow of your sigh...
私の微かな火で照らしたいだけ
I just want to illuminate it with my faint flame.
We choose to know
The struggles of this scuffed up page we're giving in
The struggles of this scuffed-up page we're giving in
土砂に汚れて be real, it hurts to grow
Stained in mud and dirt, be real, it hurts to grow.
Believing in a world of hate is overrated
まあでも貴方は美しいのだから
Well, even so, because you are beautiful.
Must be something surreal
An endless dream we can't heal
This rusted world wound up real
Still wanna love the way it feels
Late nights, the city feels dead, sure, but like
The lights and sights and sounds are treasures
こんな世界に
In a world like this,
抗って歩く力なんて
the strength to defy it and keep walking...
私にはないけど
...is something I don't have, but...
Face up, this world can't kill that inner spark
Why don't we turn this scuffed up page we're writing in
Why don't we turn this scuffed-up page we're writing in?
こんな世界じゃ be real, I think we know
In a world like this, be real, I think we know.
この夜明け is rarely fair, decide your fate
This dawn is rarely fair, decide your fate.
It's your life 貴方を捨ててしまわないで
It's your life, don't throw away who you are.
Tomorrow's a brand new day
Like all those optimists say
But the truth is rather ruthless, it might be rain
The question is, will you bear that pain?
What's your reason to stay?
This shining world led astray
Won't leave it all to decay
I choose to love it anyway
When you choose to know
The struck-out stars of the sky
A page we live in
So don't give in
...and you DEAD BEATS!!
Happy 5 years.
Here's to more.
What are you still doing here?
The show's over.
Go watch the music video!
Thank you Yulie's and Analysts for the 3D.
Bye!